question_data = [
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by "
                    "Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Pluto is a planet.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "One of Donald Trump&#039;s 2016 Presidential Campaign promises was to build a border wall between the United States and Mexico.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
